[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "How seriously should we be taking it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, I mean if you talk to Russian officials they insist that this is going to be the safest winter games ever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "So far so good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Are you psyched?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Does that stress you out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yesterday, we were doing processing and then we were traveling all morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Yeah?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "AIA SHIBUTAN: Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sochi"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "And any message you want to send back home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "You know, hey everyone we're in Sochi.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "I mean you've covered many events on your time, do you fell reasonably secure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "I have to say yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ivan Watson"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Ivan Watson, thank you very much indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Bob, if you were involved in the counterterrorist operation here, what would your biggest worry be now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Airplanes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Is that indicative to your mind that they are really expecting something to happen or that is being ultra cautious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I think they are serious about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "I mean this is clearly something they're going to be serious about it, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "AER: Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Winston, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Do you have any chance of getting a medal, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Piers, I never like to tell the world what the Jamaican team go to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Do you slightly resent the fact that people don't perhaps give you the credit and the respect you guys deserve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes they do give us the respect of course because we're from a tropical country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "New York", "JFK", "Philadelphia"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "EX", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", ":", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And if it doesn't turn up, what will you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "What we do, we have lots of people here who loved us, you know, everyone here in the village they have -- there were so, you know, the polite for us, want to lend us uniforms, stuff like that and I'm -- for our uniform our baggage was left back in New York because our flight was delayed and because they had bad weather in New York and we have to reroute it to -- well in JFK we should have landed and we have to rerouted to Philadelphia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Usain"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Has he been in touched to wish you guys luck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I've yet to hear from Usain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Seriously, what are you going to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "I am going to run for governor for the state of California.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Is it simply jealousy that he's been number one for two decades?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Yes, that's what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Yeah, he tried to be funny for everyone, he lost that edge deliberately, where is the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Jay, you know, this shows they're difficult, you know, you run a show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "That the guy is still number one in the ratings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "RBS", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Why don't we (inaudible) and start over again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Let me -- arguably, the most -- one of the most successful stand ups in the history of ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Now, Mr. Grady (ph), for fun getaways, where can you get the best bang for your buck?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Beats me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Grady"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Which was always his most important thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan O'Brien"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "So that's your excuse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Let's talk quickly about the Conan O'Brien Debacle (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Am I wrong was he blamed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I mean, well that maybe he should step aside and just let Conan take the show, maybe it wasn't right to go back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Leno"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "What do you make of Jay Leno?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I like Jay Leno.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay Leno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Is it jealousy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, of course, a lot of it is that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "About what Jerry said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Danitra Vance", "Damon Wayans"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Should Saturday Night Live, John, of being almost forced into having a more diverse star than the way that they were by pressure from the media?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Well, I think they, you know, when I was in the show, we had -- in my first year, it was Danitra Vance and Damon Wayans who are, you know, African-American, whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "PERSON": ["John"], "TIME": ["Night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What would you think about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Well, I think the day after the show goes off, he's flying to Florida with this little one nighters (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "He's not part of the family, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "So what do you think he'll do quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I think he'll do another show somewhere else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "If you are Jay Leno and you're 63 and you've had this incredible full time job for the last 22 years and suddenly you don't have it, a lot of people find that period in their lives really difficult to deal with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "In fact, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 22 years"], "PERSON": ["Jay Leno"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "What is the best way to navigate being out of a job like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Well, he has to continue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Are you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "You've never been hospitalized in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Do you get colds, flu, stuff like that or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", ",", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Very rarely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chopra Center for Wellbeing"]}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Why can't I be like you, Deepak?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "You should come and spend a week with me at the Chopra Center for Wellbeing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Deepak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "What advice do you give to people, particularly like him, who've been addicts and then being clean for long time, but still wrestled with those demons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Piers, first of all, addiction is the number one disease of our civilization and directly or indirectly, it's connected to all the other major epidemics of our time, whether it is cardiovascular illness or sudden death or suicide or overdose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]